この国の 人気の観光スポットです まだ　誰も見たことのない その屋敷を　ひと目　見ようと 標高３７２２ｍの死火山 ククルーマウンテン
Today is the tenth day.
でも　今は会えない。
It's Goreinu. Sorry to keep you waiting. What's going on?
ごめんな…」。
Do you realize it'll soon have been 240 hours
ゴン　クラピカ レオリオの３人は
Why not? Genthru's team is camping the starting point.
少しずつではあるが 屋敷に近づいていた その頃…
We decided beforehand that they
wouldn't return to the game until I sent an all clear signal.
)
I'm holding on to all the valuable cards. Doesn't that betray that they have other allies?
They'll notice if none of the four
have any important cards!
) )
They left the game at 3:05, ten days ago, right?
((それは　完璧に 仕留めたってこと？))
Yeah, in five more minutes,
their card data will be wiped.
((どうせ　どこかから　俺のこと
Essentially, they'll be out of it.
見張ってたんだろ？)) )
To be safe, we'll wait until 3:10.
)
But do you really think they've given up?
Absolutely.
)
Given that they took Battera and ran.
But they spent years collecting
those ninety-six cards.
)
Also, I'm wondering why Battera
would send his guards packing.
)
Yeah, we switched about thirty of their
ninety-six cards with fakes.
) )
I'm the one actually holding
the ninety-six cards. For such a cautious man, this is the
biggest gamble of Tsezgerra's life.
)
So I want to make sure it pays off.
((はい キルア様が　お留守の間に 執事見習として雇われました カナリアと申します))
I'm sorry, but I won't be able to
help you face Genthru's crew. Understood.
)
When do you want us to give you the card?
((いいえ　気持だけで十分です キルア様))
I'll wait until you've defeated Genthru. Good luck.
((「様」とか　つけんなよ キルアでいいよ)) ((そうは　いきません 私は使用人))
Accompany
Warp all players within
20 meters of caster to city
(must have been visited)
or player of your choice
(must have been met
inside the game).
[SR][NORM] Now it's time to go after those kids.
)
It wasn't in the plan, but we can
get Patch of Shore from them.
)
First, we need more copies of Accompany.
((お前 さっき　「暗歩」使っただろ))
Where are you right now? Near Soufrabi.
)
They're heading toward Masadora.
((相手に悟られないように 無音で歩く歩行術のことだよ))
Once they're prepared, they'll come for you. Are you ready?
((ゾルディック家では 暗殺術の基本中の基本として
Absolutely. We have you guys to thank.
最初に叩き込まれるんだ))
We need more time.
((そうでしたか　多分
But we have no choice. It'll depend on Gon.
流星街で育つうちに　自然と 身についたのだと思います)) )
Gon! Did you let our conversation
distract you and lose track?
)
Please explain what this is about.
) ((流星街は 何を捨てても許される場所))
I realize that I was being intrusive, but I took a look.
((だから　マフィアとか 「幻影旅団」の団員とかには
Your daughter?
その街の出身者が多いんです))
Or perhaps your granddaughter?
)
My lover.
((その時は 私が　ご案内しますよ)) )
She'd been hospitalized for a long time.
)
A few days ago, she passed away in her sleep.
) )
I suppose she didn't want people
thinking she wanted my money, because she returned every gift I gave her.
((歩行速度に緩急をつけて 残像を見せているんだ))
this shoddy picture frame that I made myself.
) ((侵入者のようですね それも　かなりの数の…))
All we ever needed was one other.
) ((ご主人様の命令で　今日だけは ミケは動きません))
We swore that we would never be apart...
((私の実力の程を 確かめたいそうです)) )
Until the accident that put her into a sleep from
which she'd never wake...
((ここから先は　手分けして 奴らの屋敷を探し出す)) )
Indeed... She appeared to only be sleeping...
) )
That was when I heard about Greed Island.
((あなた達がいる場所は 私有地です))
If I beat that game, I could obtain the one thing
((断りなく立ち入ることは まかり通りません)) ((お前に 俺達が止められるのか？))
Breath of Archangel
An angel that cures any
mortal injury or terminal
illness with one breath.
But angel only appears once. that I need most, like a dream come true.
((どう見ても お前に勝ち目は　ねえだろ
I was prepared to spend my
fortune on copies of that game.
まぁ　おとなしくしていれば 命だけは助けてやる)) ((その線を　一歩でも越えたら 実力で排除します))
But it doesn't matter any longer...
)
It doesn't matter...
((ボスが出るまでもねえ！ 俺達に任せてください！)) ) ) )
The kids have four copies of
Accompany among them. We have six.
)
I'll take the kid with spiky black hair.
) )
Assuming we need to resort to force.
)
Sub, take the slant-eyed kid.
What do you want? Don't be so hostile.
)
What is it? Interested now?
これだけ倒しても 息ひとつ乱れていないとは…
Stop! Talk from where you are! Yes, that's good.
((お前も　ゾルディック家の １人なのか？))
We must act like we're at a
significant disadvantage.
)
We have to convince them
((あなた方の実力では ゾルディック家の人は　おろか
that we're being forced into this position.
執事の所にすら たどり着けません))
It's quite simple.
) )
We'll beat the game on everyone's behalf,
then everyone returns to the real world.
)
And we'll split Battera's reward.
I find that hard to believe. We've had a change of heart.
)
And Tsezgerra has already left the game.
But that doesn't prove that
he agreed to your offer.
)
You have a valid point.
Then, what now? Do you want to die?
)
You've revealed your true colors. Book! Accompany on!
((フッ…　ハンターとして お前のような小娘に 負けるわけにはいかねえ))
Three more times.
)
One more time... Return
Warp to a city
of your choice.
(Must be a city
you have visited.)
[LR][NORM]
)
Masadora?
) )
Are they trying to obtain more spell cards? They might try to escape to the
real world through the port.
)
Accompany on.
((ヒィ！　すまねえ！ 命だけは　お助けを！))
They haven't been here. Did they head for the port?
)
Tsk, guess we have no choice.
Accompany on! Gon!
)
Don't lose sight of them! We're out of Accompany cards!
We'll never let you have them! Everything's gone to plan.
)
If we have to hand over our
cards, we'd rather fight! Wait, Gon!
)
Damn... Good.
Now we only need to separate them.
) )
Bisky, you run for it! B-But... Just run!
)
Wait! Hey, you aren't getting away.
I'm counting on you guys.
)
You know that I'm the Bomber?
I heard it from Tsezgerra.
)
Incredible.
ゴン…。
There aren't too many people
大丈夫なの？ ああ　気絶しているだけだ。
Whoever surrenders first has
to give up all his cards. You seem to have the wrong idea.
うぅ…　起きな！
This is your last chance to make a deal. Otherwise, you're nothing more than a thief.
ん？　あぁ　兄貴　おはよう。
I'd rather die than hand
over my cards to a thief! You can kill me, but I still
won't take out my binder!
今　何時？
You're insane.
いい気になるなよ　キル！ そんなぁ。
And I don't mean my kind of insane. Very well.
俺　兄貴を刺しちゃったこと すっげぇ反省してるよ。
You have a deal. Book.
ごめん　悪かったよ　兄貴。
I'm holding one hundred thirty-one cards.
ウソつけ！
I have ninety-seven of the restricted slot cards. I have one hundred and two cards.
やっぱ　分かる？ うん！
Book. You have #2 and #75, correct?
[TEL] チッ。
Yeah. Book.
はい。 あぁ　ママ？　うんうん…。
That's all I need.
うん　分かった。
An excellent show of Ren...
キル！　お前の友達 とうとう 執事室の近くまで来たそうだぜ。
But clearly, he has much
room for improvement.
フフフ…　どうする？　キル。 俺がママに頼めば　３人とも…。
Offense is the strongest defense. You're strong enough that
ミルキ。
a single explosion won't be
enough to finish you off.
３人に手を出したら…　殺すぜ。
So stay on the attack!
紹介が遅れましたね。
But his use of aura is sloppy at best.
私は　キルアの母です この子は　カルト。
Not sure why he was so confident.
キルアが俺達に会えないのは 何でですか？
At this point, you're nowhere near his level. You won't be able to deal significant damage.
独房にいるからです。 独房？
But continue to attack!
キルは私を刺し　兄を刺し 家を飛び出しました。
Because he will still defeat you.
キルは　自分のしたことを反省し 自ら戻って来ました。
You still haven't answered my question. Who told you about my power?
そして今は　自分の意思で 独房に入っています。
Well, it isn't important now.
ですから　キルが いつ　そこから出て来るかは…。 まぁ！　お義父様ったら！ 何をなさるおつもり!?
My point is that I don't need my ability to deal with you.
勝手なことをしないで！ せっかく戻って来たのに　もう!! 入るぞ
All according to plan. Once he's seen how much stronger he is, we'll begin to lure him into our trap! Osu!
でも　ゼノじいちゃん こいつ　全然反省してないんだぜ！
I'll make him use his power...
んなことは分かっとる。
I'll carry out the plan afterwards!
キル　もう行っていいぞ。
Looks like you need a little more pain!
だから　おとなしく 殴られてやったんだよ。
Use your power.
何!?
I have a surprise for you!
キル　シルバが呼んどるからな。
I see what you're thinking. I won't use it!
うぅ！ クッソ！　大体　じいちゃんは キルアに甘過ぎるんだよ！
Damned kid!
だから あいつが　つけ上がるんだ！
She's faster than I expected.
あいつは特別だからな。
Book!
ミル　お前から見て キルアの力量は　どうだ？
She should be out of teleportation spells. What's she doing?
そりゃ　すごいよ。 ほう…。
She used Transform to hide
it as a different card?
才能だけなら
Accompany on!
長いゾルディック家の歴史の中で ピカイチじゃない？
To Soufrabi! Accompany?
それは　ママも認めてるし 俺も　そう思う。
Why?
でも　暗殺者としては失格だな むらっ気があってさ。 「むらっ気」？
I don't get it...
友達なんか　つくってる奴に ゾルディック家は継げないよ。
Why would you go to all this
trouble to be alone with me?
要するに　あいつは弱虫なんだよ 精神的にさ。
One reason... Because I didn't want to let you cry for help.
そういうことだな。
Huh? I have no idea what you're talking about.
ねっ　その点　俺は
You're such a fool...
依頼があれば いつでも誰でも始末するぜ。
I'm telling you that I'm stronger.
超小型でさ メスの蚊に取り付けて その蚊がターゲットの血を 吸った瞬間に爆発するんだぜ。
Damned brat!
お前は　頭はいいが バカなところが　玉にきずだ。
Your attacks are too weak...
あぁ…！ まったく　お義父様ったら！
You can't defeat me!
私　急用ができましたので では　これで。
I won't hold back...
待ってください！
So don't blame me.
俺達　まだ　しばらく この街にいます。
That's what I was going to say.
キルアに　そう伝えてください。
I was being nice, so I let you hit me once.
分かりました　言っておきましょう それでは。
Because I can't restrain myself when I revert.
あなた達　何？ キルアの友達だよ。
And I end up killing my opponents!
はい　お母様。
Oh, you're alive?
言っちゃあ何だが 薄気味悪い連中だな。
Why would you... hide your power?
キルアが　自分から「会えない」 って言ったのもウソくせぇ。
Two reasons... The ace up your sleeve should remain hidden...
ゴン　このまま戻るのは シャクだぜ。 無理にでも　ついて行かねえか？
And more than anything, I hate the way I look.
うん　でも　そうすると きっと彼女が　責任を とらされるような気がするから。
Too macho! Don't you agree?
あっ　そっか…。
He can't hear me anymore?
そこなら　屋敷に直接つながる 電話があるから
I have a slight advantage in martial
skill and physical strength.
ゼノ様が　お出になられれば あるいは…。
But he has me beat in aura capacity.
ゼノ様って？ キルア様のおじい様です。
I probably won't be able to hurt
him with any normal attack.
うん。
I can't afford to fool around.
そうか。
Wrong. Experiment #1...
試験は　どうだった？
Lightning Palm! Lightning Palm
キル　こっちに来い。 えっ？
Doesn't seem to be enough to knock him out. But I can immobilize him for a few seconds.
お前の話を聞きたい。
Okay. Experiment #2...
試験で　どんなことをして
A yo-yo?
誰と出会い　何を思ったのか。
Let's do this.
どんなことでもいい　教えてくれ。
What's he up to?
お義父様ってば 私に　何の断りもなく…。
What's that thing made of?
あら　キルったら パパとばかり楽しそうに…。
This is a superalloy yo-yo my brother ordered.
許せないわ。
It weighs around fifty kilograms, so it packs quite a punch!
でさ　そしたらゴンが 何て言ったと思う？
Whoa!
ハハハ…。 アハっ。
Damn...
わがままだろ？ 面白い子だな。
Between the weight and centrifugal
force, that really hurts.
それで今度は　剣を眉間に 突きつけられたんだけどさ
He always leaves his right side exposed
それでもゴンは…。 キル。
when I attack a certain way!
えっ？ 友達に会いたいか？ 遠慮することはない　正直に言え。
If I take his yo-yo, leaving him empty-handed, he'll make the same mistake!
思えば…
My chance!
お前と親子として 話をしたことなど　なかったな。
There!
俺が親に暗殺者として 育てられたように
Time to crush you!
お前にも それを強要してしまった。
Oh?
俺と　お前は違う お前が出て行くまで
Did I forget to mention that I have two yo-yos?
そんな簡単なことに 気づかなかった。
Wow, you're still conscious?
お前は俺の子だ。
Did you know that when you kick me, you raise your
guarding arm on the other side?
だが　お前は　お前だ。
You're creating your own blind spot.
好きに生きろ。 疲れたら いつでも戻って来ればいい　なっ。
He used my blind spot to pull
out a yo-yo and attack? Then your defensive habit...
もう一度　聞く。
Was a fake to make you
kick me with your left leg.
仲間に会いたいか？
And when you released your first yo-yo...
うん。 分かった。
I knew you picked up something to throw at me.
お前は　もう自由だ。
Why did you use Accompany to
draw me away from the others?
だが…。
To make you focus on a one-on-one chance,
so you'd lose track of your surroundings.
一つだけ誓え。
I don't believe it..
絶対に仲間を裏切るな　いいな。
You set three traps during that brief exchange?
うん。
Three? You must be joking...
誓うよ　裏切らない。
Every move I made was a trap.
キル。
Both work.
無駄よ　３人は帰ったわ 独房に戻りなさい。 イヤだ　俺　行くよ。
Why won't you accept your fate?
キル!!
You can't beat me.
はっ…！
No way.
どけよ。
I haven't lost yet!
ハハハ　あぁ　キル
I was mistaken.
何て冷たい目が できるようになったの。
I take back what I said. You are strong...
一体　何を考えてるの？ せっかくキルが戻って来たのに！ しばらく　好きにさせとけよ。
This battle is mental, not physical.
ダメよ　何　言ってるの！
I must crush his will.
キルが 立派な後継者になれるかどうか 今が一番大切な時期なのよ！
His will to fight, his will to stand, his will to resist.
分かってるじゃねえか　じゃあ
Otherwise, he'll never admit defeat...
つべこべ言わずに黙ってろ！
To win, I must swallow my
pride and play it smart.
フフフ…　いつか　必ず戻って来る。
Let me demonstrate that all your hard
work and confidence mean nothing!
キルアを自由の身にしながら 必ず暗殺者として戻って来ると 確信するシルバ
The devilish man has unleashed his true power.
そして 執事室へと向かったゴン達は
Can Gon emerge victorious?